one two three four
if i find him
if i just follow love
would he hold me
and never let me go
would he let me borrow his moment to go
at the train station
three stops from her home
there's an airplane in the sky
hey there
how you doing
hi
my name's mary
there's no way to
the house of the house
just when my grandma and the grandfather
you
and it's always been my home away from home
i grew up playing in the backyard
swinging on the swing set
no idea where the real world was
or how crazy it gets
playing hide and seek with my cousins in the trees
no clue
then
how much it all would mean to me
to the ones that taught me love
big and strong
on sunday mornings we would drive down to the beach
all of us kids piled into the back seat
run up and down the dunes
and jump over the